Guide to the University Archives photograph collection, 1861-ongoing UA.01.15.0009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
University Archives photograph collection
1861-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. University Archives
UA.01.15.0009
46.5 Linear Feet
The University Archives Photograph Collection was compiled by University Archives staff from a variety of sources for use in research and teaching. The University Archives Photograph Collection consists of approx. 51000 photographic prints, negatives, slides, illustrations, and a few daguerreotypes. The majority of the collection was generated by Duke University Photography, student publications, and university publications. Subjects include Duke University administrators, faculty, staff, students, alumni, and visitors; Duke University athletics, academic programs, events, student life, reunions, commencements, and other activities; and scenes of Duke University's West and East campuses, the Trinity College campuses (Durham, N.C. and Randolph County, N.C.), campus facilities, campus architecture, Durham, Randolph County, and other related buildings and locations. Also included are some photographs separated from other University Archives collections.
Online Items
Selected images from this collection have been digitized and are available in the Duke Yearlook photostream on Flickr..
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The University Archives Photograph Collection received by the University Archives from a variety of sources, 1972-2022.
Biographical/Historical note
The University Archives Photograph Collection was compiled by University Archives staff from a variety of sources for use in research and teaching.
Collection Overview
The University Archives Photograph Collection consists of approx. 51,000 photographic prints, negatives, slides, illustrations, and a few daguerreotypes. The majority of the collection was generated by Duke University News Service, Duke University Photography, student publications, and university publications. The collection is arranged into four series: People, Activities, Buildings, and Separated Photographs. The People Series (33 boxes, approx. 16,500 items) includes portraits and other photographs of individuals related to Duke University, such as presidents, trustees, administrators, faculty, staff, students, alumni, and visitors. The Activities Series (44 boxes, approx. 22,000 items) consists of photographs of University groups and events, including commencements, reunions, athletic teams, academic departments, campus demonstrations, student activities, and other group photographs. The Buildings Series includes scenes of Duke University's West and East campuses, the Trinity College campuses (Durham, N.C. and Randolph County, N.C.), campus facilities, campus architecture, Durham, Randolph County, and other related buildings and locations. The Separated Photographs Series (3 boxes, aprrox. 1,000 items) consists of images separated from other University Archives collections for preservation and access.
Related Material
Duke University Archives Photographic Negative Collection, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Black-and-white photographs; Color photographs; Daguerreotypes (photographs); Negatives (photographs); Slides (photographs); Duke University -- Alumni and alumnae; Duke University -- Administration; Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University -- Buildings; Duke University -- Students; Duke University -- History; Duke University. News Service; Duke University. University Archives
- People Series, 33 Boxes, approx. 16,500 items
  - Unidentified Photographs (Box 1)
  - Abele, Julian F. (Box 1)
  - Abelles, Paul W. (Box 1)
  - Acomb, Frances D. (Box 1)
  - Adams, James (Box 1)
  - Addoms, Ruth M. (Box 1)
  - Adelman, Mark (Box 1)
  - Ader, Paul (Box 1)
  - Adler, Alexandra (Box 1)
  - Alden, John (History) (Box 1)
  - Aldridge, Fred S. (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Jaylynn (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Leo (Box 1)
  - Allen, George G. (Box 1)
  - Allen, George V. (Box 1)
    - Alyea, E.P. (Box 1)
  - Alspaugh, John W. (Box 1)
  - Amaker, Tommy [Basketball] (Box 1)
  - Amos, Dennis Bernard (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Hugh (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Lewis (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Roger F. [Forestry] (Box 1)
  - Anderson, William Banks (Box 1)
  - Anlyan, William (Box 1)
  - Apgar, Lawrence Clarke (Box 1)
  - Applewhite, James (Box 1)
  - Archie, William C. (Box 1)
  - Arena, Jay (Box 1)
  - Arnold, H.B., 1890s [Faculty, Trinity College, 1890s] (Box 1)
  - Arnold, Ralph (Box 1)
  - Ashmore, Frank L. (Box 1)
  - Asirratham, E. (Box 1)
  - Atwood, Theodore W. (Box 1)
  - Aviles, Luis, Jr. (Box 1)
  - Baade, Hans W. (Box 1)
  - Back, Kurt W. (Box 1)
  - Baez, Joan (Box 1)
  - Bagley, Charles R. [Class of 1914, Duke's First Rhodes Scholar] (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Joseph [Zoology] (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Josiah W. [Senator] (Box 1)
  - Baker, Bessie (Box 1)
  - Baker, Frank (Box 1)
  - Baker, Lenox Dial (Box 1)
  - Baldwin, Alice Mary, Portraits (Box 2)
  - Baldwin, Alice Mary, Group Photos, Snapshots (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Ball, Margaret (Box 2)
  - Banham, Katharine (Box 2)
  - Barber, James David (Box 2)
  - Barbour, George B. (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Evelyn (Box 2)
  - Barnes, James Foster, 4 folders (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Robert H. (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Robert L. (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Myrtle (Preyer) (Box 2)
  - Barzun, Jacques (Box 2)
  - Basinger, Reaves H., Jr. (Box 2)
  - Bassett, Frank (Box 2)
  - Bassett, John Spencer (Box 2)
  - Bassett, Robert V.R. (Box 2)
  - Baum, Paull Franklin (Box 2)
  - Baylis, Charles A. (Box 2)
  - Beach, Waldo [Divinity School] (Box 2)
  - Bear, Warren C. (Box 2)
  - Beard, Joseph W. and Dorothy W. (Box 2)
  - Beare, Robert Livingston (Box 2)
  - Becker, R. Frederick (Box 2)
  - Behrens, Helen (Box 3)
  - Benedict, Barbara A. (Box 3)
  - Bennett, Ben (Box 3)
  - Berkley, Kenneth H. (Box 3)
  - Berninger, Oscar August (Box 3)
  - Berry, Martha (Box 3)
  - Berry, Thomas S. (Box 3)
  - Berry, Willard (Box 3)
  - Bevan, William (Box 3)
  - Bevington, Helen (Box 3)
  - Bevington, Merle M. (Box 3)
  - Biddle, A.J.D. (Box 3)
  - Biddle, Mary Duke (Box 3)
  - Bigelow, Lucius Aurelius (Box 3)
  - Biggs, E. Power (Box 3)
  - Binkley, Robert W. (Box 3)
  - Bird, Harold C. (Box 3)
  - Bivins / Carr [Fannie White Carr, Mrs. Joseph; Carr, Ida Z.] (Box 3)
  - Black, David E. (Box 3)
  - Black, Martin Lee, Jr. (Box 3)
  - Blackburn, John, 1970 [Provost] (Box 3)
  - Blackburn, William A., 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Blair, Claude M. (Box 3)
  - Blake, J. Donald (Box 3)
  - Blakely, Florence (Box 3)
  - Blaney, Bernie (Box 3)
  - Bladon, Colin (Box 3)
  - Block, Martin (Box 3)
  - Blomquist, Hugo Leander (Box 3)
  - Bly, Chauncey G. (Box 3)
  - Bly, James R. (Box 3)
  - Boaz, Ralph P. (Box 3)
  - Bock, George (Box 3)
  - Bogdonoff, Morton (Box 3)
  - Bolich, William Bryan (Box 3)
  - Bolling, Richard (Box 3)
  - Bolmeier, Edward C. (Box 4)
  - Bonawit, G. Owen (Box 4)
  - Bond, Juliam H., 1999 [Speaker at Martin Luther King Festivities] (Box 4)
  - Bone, Allan [Photos from News Service File] (Box 4)
  - Bonk, James [See also Oversize Photos] (Box 4)
  - Bookhout, C.G. (Box 4)
  - Boone, Charles C. (Box 4)
  - Booth, Rachel A. [Nursing] (Box 4)
  - Borstelmann, Lloyd J. (Box 4)
  - Bosley, Harold (Box 4)
  - Bowers, Frank [See Oversize "Whitford" for Original] (Box 4)
  - Boyce, Benjamin (Box 4)
  - Boyd, Julian P. (Box 4)
  - Boyd, William Kenneth (Box 4)
  - Brabanti, Ralph J.D. [Also Brabanti, Jr.] (Box 4)
  - Bradley, Harold L. (Box 4)
  - Bradley, Scully (Box 4)
  - Bradsher, Charles K. [Chemistry] (Box 4)
  - Bradway, John Saeger [Law] (Box 4)
  - Branscomb, Bennett Harvie (Box 4)
  - Breedlove, Joseph Penn (Box 4)
  - Brees, Anton (Box 4)
  - Bressler, Bernard, M.D. (Box 4)
  - Brice, Ashbel G. [Duke Press] (Box 4)
  - Bridges, Furman A. (Box 4)
  - Brim, Kenneth M. (Box 4)
  - Brinkley, Roberta Florence (Box 4)
  - Brinkley, William L. (Box 4)
  - Broadhead, Edward Hall (Box 4)
  - Broce, Thomas Edwards (Box 4)
  - Broderson, Robert (Box 4)
  - Brodie, H. Keith H. (Box 4)
  - Brodie, H. Keith H. [Inauguration and Inauguration Activities] (Box 4)
  - Brodie, H. Keith H. (Box 4)
  - Bronfenbrenner, Martin (Box 4)
  - Brooks, Cleanth (Box 4)
  - Brooks, Eugene Clyde (Box 4)
  - Broughton, Joseph M. [Governor] (Box 4)
  - Brower, A.S. (Box 4)
  - Brower, Dr. and "Wilmington Facilities" (Box 4)
  - Brown, Frances [Chemistry] (Box 4)
  - Brown, Frank Clyde (Box 4)
  - Brown, Joseph Gill [President of the Board of Trustees, 1917-27] (Box 5)
  - Brown, Les (Box 5)
  - Brown, Lynwood E., undated (Box 127)
    Scope and Contents
    Portrait of Lynwood E. Brown, a graduate of Trinity College at Duke University.
  - Brown, Myrtle Irene (Box 5)
  - Brownell, William (Box 5)
  - Brownlee, William H. (Box 5)
  - Bruinsma, Henry A. (Box 5)
  - Bruton, John Fletcher [Chairman of the Board of Trustees, 1927-46] (Box 5)
  - Bruton, Paul [Law] (Box 5)
  - Bryan, Edward H. (Box 5)
  - Bryan, Paul (Box 5)
  - Bryant, Joseph Allen (Box 5)
  - Bryson, Edwin Constant (Box 5)
  - Bryson, Marion R. (Box 5)
  - Bryson, Thaddeus D. (Box 5)
  - Bubas, Victor A. (Box 5)
  - Buck, Roger C. (Box 5)
  - Budd, Louis J. (Box 5)
  - Buettner-Janusch, Dr. John (Box 5)
  - Bunche, Ralph (Box 5)
  - Burke, Sonny (Box 5)
  - Burkhead, Lingurn Skidmore [President of the Board of Trustees, 1877-81] (Box 5)
  - Burlak, Jacob (Box 5)
  - Busse, Ewald (Box 5)
  - Butters, Ron (Box 5)
  - Butters, Tom, 1968 [See also Athletics - Baseball, 1968] (Box 5)
  - Cahoon, John B., Jr. (Box 5)
  - Caldwell, Hershel (Box 5)
  - Callaway, J. Lamar, M.D. (Box 5)
  - Cameron, Edmund M. [See also Eddie Cameron Scrapbooks for Photo Taken by Sports Illustrated] (Box 5)
  - Campbell, Dennis [Divinity School] (Box 5)
  - Campbell, Janet (Box 5)
  - Campbell, Jerry [Library] (Box 5)
  - Canine, William (Box 5)
  - Cannon, James F., III (Box 5)
  - Capp, Paul (Box 5)
  - Card, Wilbur Wade (Box 5)
  - Carden, Norman F. (Box 5)
  - Carlitz, Leonard [Mathematics, J.B. Duke Professor] (Box 5)
  - Carmichael, Stokley (Box 5)
  - Carr, John W., Jr. (Box 6)
  - Carr, Julian S. (Box 6)
  - Carroll, Eber Malcolm [History Department] (Box 6)
  - Carroll, Jackson W. (Box 6)
  - Carroll, Wallace (Box 6)
  - Carter, F. Bayard (Box 6)
  - Cartter, Allen Murray (Box 6)
  - Cartwright, William Holman (Box 6)
  - Castellano, Juan (Box 6)
  - Cathcart, A.M. (Box 6)
  - Cavaliere, A. Ralph (Box 6)
  - Cavers, David Farquhar [Law School] (Box 6)
  - Cell, John W. "Jack" (Box 6)
  - Chafe, Bill (Box 6)
  - Chaffin, Nora (Box 6)
  - Chaiken, Leon E. [Forestry] (Box 6)
  - Chambers, Robert Luther (Box 6)
  - Chappell, C.G., Dr. (Box 6)
  - Chappell, Fred (Box 6)
  - Charlesworth, James H. [Religion] (Box 6)
  - Cheasty, Denise [Duke Student in China] (Box 6)
  - Cheek, Roma Sawyer (Box 6)
  - Chernoff, Amoz I. (Box 6)
  - Cherry, R.G. [Governor] (Box 6)
  - Childs, B.G. (Box 6)
  - Christ, Robert W. (Box 6)
  - Christie, George [Law School] (Box 6)
  - Church, Austin E. (Box 6)
  - Church, Frank (Box 6)
  - Ciaroi, John (Box 6)
  - Ciompi, Giorgio [See also Ciompi Quartet (Activities)] (Box 6)
  - Clark, Chris W. (Box 6)
  - Clark, Elon (Box 6)
  - Clark, Grover (Box 6)
  - Clark, Kenneth Willis (Box 6)
  - Clark, Ramsey (Box 6)
  - Clay, A.T. (Box 6)
  - Clay, Susan (Box 6)
  - Cleaveland, Frederick (Box 6)
  - Cleland, James T. (Box 7)
  - Clogan, Paul Maurice (Box 7)
  - Closs, William [19th Century Methodist Minister, Trinity Trustee] (Box 7)
  - Clyde, Paul H. (Box 7)
  - Cocke, Norman Atwater [Chairman of the Board of Trustees, 1954-60] (Box 7)
  - Coffin, Henry Sloane (Box 7)
  - Cohen, Sanford (Box 7)
  - Coile, Theodore Stanley (Box 7)
  - Coker, Jerry (Box 7)
  - Cole, Robert Taylor (Box 7)
  - Coles [Visiting Professor] (Box 7)
  - Colton, Joel (Box 7)
  - Colver, Robert M., 1914 [Department of Education] (Box 7)
  - Como, Perry (Box 7)
  - Conant, Norman F. [ ] (Box 7)
  - Conner, George W. (Box 7)
  - Connery, Robert H. (Box 7)
  - Conover, Richard M. (Box 7)
  - Constant, Frank Woodbridge (Box 7)
  - Cook, Clark Curtis (Box 7)
  - Cook, Samuel Dubois (Box 7)
  - Coombs, Jack [Baseball Coach] (Box 7)
  - Corbitt, Ken (Box 7)
  - Cowper, Frederick Augustus (Box 7)
  - Cox, Billy (Box 7)
  - Cox, Hilden T. (Box 7)
  - Cox, Robert Boyd (Box 7)
  - Cranford, William Ivey (Box 7)
  - Craven, Braxton (Box 7)
  - Craven, J. Braxton, Jr. (Box 7)
  - Creadick, Robert N. (Box 7)
  - Crispell, Raymond (Box 7)
  - Cronkite, Walter (Box 7)
  - Crowder, Dick (Box 7)
  - Crowell, John Franklin (Box 7)
  - Crum, Mason (Box 7)
  - Culberson, William L., 1963 [Botany] (Box 7)
  - Cunningham, Bert [Department of Zoology] (Box 7)
  - Currie, Brainerd (Box 7)
  - Curtiss, John Shelton (Box 7)
  - Cushman, Robert E. (Box 7)
  - Dacus, Edwin E. [Head of Hillsborough Quarry] (Box 7)
  - Dagg, John Leadley (Box 8)
  - Dai, Bingham [Professor of Psychiatry] (Box 8)
  - Dale, Julia (Box 8)
  - Dale, Kathleen Watkins (Box 8)
  - Dalton, Harry [Donor] (Box 8)
  - Daly, Chuck (Charles J.) [See "Vic Bubas"] (Box 8)
  - Daniels, Boyd L. (Box 8)
  - Daniels, Jonathan W. (Box 8)
  - Davison, Wilburt C. (Box 8)
  - Day, John F. (Box 8)
  - Dean, Dayton (Box 8)
  - Dean, Gordon Evans (Box 8)
  - DeBrunner, Hans E. (Box 8)
  - DeConde, Alexander (Box 8)
  - DeGravelles, William David (Box 8)
  - DeHart, James (Box 8)
  - Delaplane, Walter Harold (Box 8)
  - Dellinger, David C. [Business Administration] (Box 8)
  - Dellinger, Walter [Law School] (Box 8)
  - DeMaria, William J.A. (Box 8)
  - Demorest, Jean-Jacques (Box 8)
  - DeMott, Debra (Box 8)
  - Dent, Dr. Sarah (Box 8)
  - Derogatis, Al [Football Player] (Box 8)
  - DeVyver, Frank T. (Box 8)
  - Diamond, Irving (Box 8)
  - DiBona, Joseph D. (Box 8)
  - Dicks, Russell (Box 8)
  - Djordjevic, Milan (Box 8)
  - Dole, Elizabeth Hanford [Commencement 1985], 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Donley, Beatrice (Box 8)
  - Douglas, William O. [With Horack, H.C.] (Box 8)
  - Dovenmuehle, Robert H. (Box 8)
  - Dowd, Jerome (Box 8)
  - Doxey, John Elwood (Box 8)
  - Dozier, John M. (Box 8)
  - Droege, R.C. (Box 8)
  - Dubose, Robert N. (Box 8)
  - Dubs, Homer (Box 8)
  - Duffey, Bernard (Box 8)
  - Duke Family (Box 9)
  - Duke, Angier Biddle (Box 9)
  - Duke, Angier Buchanan (Box 9)
  - Duke, Artelia Roney (Box 9)
  - Duke, Anthony Drexel (Box 9)
  - Duke, B.N. (Box 9)
  - Duke, Brodie (Box 9)
  - Duke, Doris (Box 9)
  - Duke, James Buchanan (Box 9)
  - Duke, James Buchanan [Christening Ceremony] (Box 9)
  - Duke, James Buchanan [Death and Burial] (Box 9)
  - Duke, James Buchanan [Death Mask] (Box 9)
  - Duke, John Taylor (Box 9)
  - Duke, Mary Lyon (Box 10)
  - Duke, Nanaline Holt Inman [(Mrs. J.B. Duke)] (Box 10)
  - Duke, Sarah P.A. [(Mrs. B.N. Duke)] (Box 10)
  - Duke, Washington (Box 10)
  - Duke, William James [Uncle Billy] (Box 10)
  - Dukes, Charles Aubrey (Box 10)
  - Dulles, Eleanor Lansing (Box 10)
  - Dumas, Paul (Box 10)
  - Duncan, Lt. Col. Charles H. (Box 10)
  - Dunlop, Connie [Library] (Box 10)
  - Dunning, Stephen (Box 10)
  - Durham, Robert L. (Box 10)
  - Durden, Robert (Box 10)
  - Durham, Stonewall (Box 10)
  - Dwire, Henry Rudolph (Box 10)
  - Ebert, Dr. Paula (Box 10)
  - Echieverri, Humberto (Box 10)
  - Eddy, Ruth (Box 10)
  - Edens, A. Hollis, Pre-Duke (Box 10)
  - Edens, A. Hollis, Portraits (Box 10)
  - Edens, A. Hollis, Inauguration (Box 10)
  - Edens, Mrs. A. Hollis (Box 10)
  - Edwards, Charles W. (Box 10)
  - Edwards, Ray I. (Box 10)
  - Ehlhardt, George Brinkmann (Box 10)
  - Eisdorfer, Carl (Box 10)
  - Elliott, W.W. (Box 11)
  - Eisenhower, Julie Nixon (Box 11)
  - Eiteman, Wilford (Box 11)
  - Elchepp, Jane G., M.D. (Box 11)
  - Ellwood, Charles Abram and Ida M. (Box 11)
  - Engel, Frank (Box 11)
  - Ervin, Sam (Box 11)
  - Eslinger, Richard [Divinity] (Box 11)
  - Estes, E. Harvey, Jr., M.D. (Box 11)
  - Everett, Palmatier (Box 11)
  - Farley, James A. (Box 11)
  - Fearing, Robert Beveridge (Box 11)
  - Fein, J.M., M.D. (Box 11)
  - Fendt, Paul F. (Box 11)
  - Fenton, Charles A. (Box 11)
  - Ferguson, Charles E. (Box 11)
  - Ferguson, Robert (Box 11)
  - Few, Benjamin F. [Vice-Chairman of Duke Endowment] (Box 11)
  - Few, William Preston [Portraits] (Box 11)
  - Few, William Preston [Snapshots and Groups] (Box 11)
  - Few, William Preston [Childhood and Youth] (Box 11)
  - Few, William Preston [Family] (Box 11)
  - Few, William Preston [Death and Burial] (Box 11)
  - Fillmore, Richard [Director of Duke Gardens] (Box 11)
  - Filston, Howard [Pediatric Surgery] (Box 11)
  - Finch, Thomas (Box 11)
  - Fisher, Adrian [Former U.N. Ambassador] (Box 11)
  - Fisher, Eric (Box 11)
  - Fitzgerald, William S. (Box 11)
  - Fleishman, Joel, 1984, Group Photo (Box 11)
  - Flannery, Harry (Box 11)
  - Flowers, Robert Lee [Youth] (Box 12)
  - Flowers, Robert Lee [Group Photos], 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Flowers, Robert Lee [Portraits] (Box 12)
  - Flowers, Robert Lee, 1887-91 [Naval Academy Scenes], 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Flowers, Robert Lee [Family] (Box 12)
  - Fonda, Jane (Box 12)
  - Forbus, Wiley D. (Box 12)
  - Ford, Gerald R. (Box 12)
  - Forlines, John A., Jr. (Box 12)
  - Foster, Bill (Box 13)
  - Fountain, Grigg [Divinity School?] (Box 13)
  - Fowlie, Wallace [See also photos of W.D. Davies] (Box 13)
  - Frank, Gerald (Box 13)
  - Frankel, Charles (Box 13)
  - Franklin, John Hope (Box 13)
  - Freeman, John (Box 13)
  - French, Charles F. [Class of 1939] (Box 13)
  - Frenzel, Charles, Jr. (Box 13)
  - Friedburg, Ruth (Box 13)
  - Friedl, Ernestine (Box 13)
  - Frost, Robert (Box 13)
  - Frye, John [Class of 1961] (Box 13)
  - Fuller, Edgar (Box 13)
  - Fuller, Lon (Box 13)
  - Funderburk, M. Laney [Alumni Affairs] (Box 13)
  - Fuqua, John Brooks (Box 13)
  - Furlow, John (Box 13)
  - Fuson, Bob (Box 13)
  - Garber, Paul Neff (Box 13)
  - Gallie, Tom (Box 13)
  - Galloway, Karen [School of Law, Class of 1974] (Box 13)
  - Gardner, Clarence E., Jr. (Box 13)
  - Garmezy, Norman (Box 13)
  - Garrard, Anne (Box 13)
  - Gates, Arthur Mathews (Box 13)
  - Gates, Henry "Skip" (Box 13)
  - Gaver, Otto Hans (Box 13)
  - Gehman, W. Scott (Box 13)
  - Gellhorn, Ernest [Law School] (Box 13)
  - Georgiade (Box 13)
  - Gerard, Frank (Box 13)
  - Gergen, John J. [Math Department], 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Gibson, Elizabeth (Box 13)
  - Gibson, William M. (Box 13)
  - Gilbert, Allan (Box 13)
  - Gilbert, Katharine [Philosophy Department] (Box 13)
  - Giles Sisters, 1970 [from Alumni Register] (Box 13)
  - Gillin, Donald (Box 13)
  - Gillin, John P. (Box 13)
  - Gminski, Mike (Box 13)
  - Ginsberg, Allen (Box 13)
  - Githens, Sherwood (Box 13)
  - Glasson, Harold (Box 13)
  - Glasson, William Henry [Political Science Faculty, Graduate School Dean, See also Glasson Papers for Family Pictures] (Box 13)
  - Glenn, Dr. James F. (Box 13)
  - Glocker, George (Box 13)
  - Gobbel, Luther (Box 13)
  - Gohdes, Clarence Louis Frank (Box 13)
  - Goodson, W. Kenneth [Divinity Adjunct] (Box 13)
  - Goodling, Richard A. (Box 13)
  - Gordy, Walter (Box 14)
  - Gossett, William T. (Box 14)
  - Graham, Billy, 1951 (Box 14)
  - Gray, C.T. (Box 14)
  - Gray, Gordon (Box 14)
  - Gray, Irving E. (Box 14)
  - Greene, Balcomb (Box 14)
  - Greene, W.K. (Box 14)
  - Greenhill, Maurice (Box 14)
  - Greer, J.G. (Box 14)
  - Gregg, Robert C. [Divinity School] (Box 14)
  - Gregory, Dick, 1969 [Afro-American Week] (Box 14)
  - Greuling, Eugene (Box 14)
  - Griffith, William [Student Affairs] (Box 14)
  - Griffiths, Phillip A. (Box 14)
  - Griggs, Lillian Baker (Box 14)
  - Grimson, Keith S. (Box 14)
  - Grist, William T. (Box 14)
  - Groat, Dick (Box 14)
  - Gross, Paul Magnus (Box 14)
  - Grout, Julia Rebecca (Box 14)
  - Gruber, Karl (Box 14)
  - Grzybowski, Kazimierz (Box 14)
  - Guibor, George (Box 14)
  - Gulick, Floyd (Box 14)
  - Gustavson, R.G. (Box 14)
  - Gutekunst, John (Box 14)
  - Guy, David (Box 14)
  - Hagler, Elias P. (Box 14)
  - Haines, Howard (Box 14)
  - Halifax, Lord, 1945 [Visit during WWII, See also scrapbook] (Box 14)
  - Hall, Frank Gregory (Box 14)
  - Hall, Professor Hugh M. (Box 14)
  - Hall, Louise (Box 14)
  - Hall, Thor (Box 14)
  - Hall, William Holland (Box 14)
  - Hallowell, John (Box 14)
  - Hamilton, Earl J. (Box 14)
  - Hamilton, Professor William (Box 14)
  - Hamblin, Edwing (Box 14)
  - Hammond, J. Samuel [Carillonneur, Library] (Box 15)
  - Handler, Philip (Box 15)
  - Hanes, Frederic Moir (Box 15)
  - Hanes, Mrs. Frederick Moir (Box 15)
  - Hanes, P. Frank (Box 15)
  - Hanes, P. Huber, Jr. and Sr. (Box 15)
  - Hanford, Liddie [See Elizabeth "Liddie" Hanford Dole] (Box 15)
  - Hanks, Nancy (Box 15)
  - Hanna, Frank [Department of Economics] (Box 15)
  - Hansen-Pruss, Oscar Carl (Box 15)
  - Hanson, Earl (Box 15)
  - Hardin, Professor Grady (Box 15)
  - Hargitt, George Thomas (Box 15)
  - Harman, Dr. Charles M. (Box 15)
  - Harp, Tom (Box 15)
  - Harrar, Ellwood Scott (Scotty) (Box 15)
  - Harris, J.S. (Box 15)
  - Harris, J. Welch, Jr. (Box 15)
  - Harrison, Evelyn (Box 15)
  - Hart, Hornell (Box 15)
  - Hart, Julian Deryl (Box 15)
  - Hart, Mrs. Julian Deryl (Box 15)
  - Hartman, David (Box 15)
  - Hasbrouck, Francis M. (Box 15)
  - Hatfield, Mark (Box 15)
  - Hatley, Charles Cleveland (Box 15)
  - Hauerwas, Stanley M. (Box 15)
  - Hauser, Charles R. (Box 15)
  - Havighurst, Clark (Box 15)
  - Havrilesky, Thomas (Box 15)
  - Hays, Brooks (Box 15)
  - Haywood, Ernest Lee (Box 15)
  - Heald, Henry T. (Box 15)
  - Heckscher, William S. (Box 15)
  - Heitman, Joan Franklin (Box 15)
  - Heninger, S.K., Jr. (Box 15)
  - Heninger, S.K. (Box 15)
  - Henney, Richard B. (Box 15)
  - Henricksen, Gerhard Chester [Business & Finance, Treasurer] (Box 15)
  - Henry, Stuart [Divinity School] (Box 15)
  - Hendrix, Mildred L. (Box 15)
  - Hendrix, Mildred L. [Organs and Organists] (Box 15)
  - Hepler, C.D. (Box 16)
  - Hermelink, H.M. (Box 16)
  - Herring, Herbert J. (Box 16)
  - Hershey, Lewis B. (Box 16)
  - Hetherington, Duncan (Box 16)
  - Heydan, Dr., With patient (Box 16)
  - Hickman, Franks [See also Boston University School of Theology, Class of 1920] (Box 16)
  - Hickman, John Bamber (Box 16)
  - Hickson, A.O. (Box 16)
  - Higgens, Mary (Box 16)
  - Hill, Douglas (Box 16)
  - Hill, Lorraine (Box 16)
  - Hill, Robert L. (Box 16)
  - Hillerbrand, Hans J. (Box 16)
  - Hobbs, Marcus Edwin (Box 16)
  - Hodges, Luther (Box 16)
  - Hodges, Ronald (Box 16)
  - Hoey, Clyde Roark (Box 16)
  - Hogshead, Nancy (Box 16)
  - Hohman, Leslie (Box 16)
  - Holler, Adlai (Box 16)
  - Holton, Holland (Box 16)
  - Holler, Walker (Box 16)
  - Holmes, Edward (Box 16)
  - Hoover, Calvin Bryce (Box 16)
  - Hopkins, Dwight (Box 16)
  - Hopkins, Everett (Box 16)
  - Hopkins, Harry (Box 16)
  - Horack, H.C. (Box 16)
  - Horn, Edward C. (Box 16)
  - Horton, Charles (Box 16)
  - Houck, C.B. (Box 16)
  - Howard, Lawrence (Box 16)
  - Howard, Raymond (Box 16)
  - Howard, Reginaldo (Box 16)
  - Howell, Doris (Box 16)
  - Hubbell, Jay Broadus (Box 16)
  - Huckabee, Ellen (Box 16)
  - Huestis, Charles B. (Box 16)
  - Humm, Harold J. (Box 16)
  - Humphrey, Don D. (Box 16)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H. (Box 16)
  - Humphreys, Josephine (Box 16)
  - Hunt, Alfred M. (Box 16)
  - Hunt, Joseph M., Jr. (Box 16)
  - Hunt, "Dean" Samuel Robert (Box 16)
  - Hunter, Wanda S. (Box 16)
  - Hurlburt, Allan (Box 16)
  - Huxley, Aldous, et al (Box 16)
  - Hyatt, Robert P. (Box 17)
  - Hyman, Mac (Box 17)
  - Ilkow, Peter (Box 17)
  - Ingles, Thelma (Box 17)
  - Ingram, O. Kelly [Divinity School] (Box 17)
  - Irene, Princess of Greece [Parties, Receptions, Group Photos] (Box 17)
  - Irene, Princess of Greece [Touring Duke] (Box 17)
  - Irving, W.H. (Box 17)
  - Ivey, George M. (Box 17)
  - Jackson, Mrs. [Chapel] (Box 17)
  - Jacobansky, Ann (Box 17)